raleys.com 2019-08-02

# Online Privacy Policy: Information Collection & Use | Raley's

## We Respect Your Privacy

_Last updated February 1, 2019_  
In this age of information, you value your privacy more than ever before, and so does Raley’s. You deserve to know how Raley’s treats your private information gathered on these websites. We encourage you to read these paragraphs so that you can learn more about Raley’s website privacy policy.

BY USING RALEYS.COM, NOBHILL.COM, SOMETHINGEXTRA.COM, SHOP.RALEYS.COM, PHARMACY.RALEYS.COM, FOODFORFAMILIES.ORG, RALEYSSTORIES.COM, RALEYSLETSBEGIN.COM, FOODSOURCE.NET, OR ANY OTHER WEBSITE HOSTED BY RALEY’S OR RALEY’S AFFILIATES, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT USE THE RALEY’S FAMILY OF FINE STORES WEBSITES.

### Information Collection & Use

Raley’s and its affiliated companies are the sole owners of the information collected on raleys.com, nobhill.com, somethingextra.com and foodsource.net. We collect personally identifying information from our users at several different points on our websites.

### Registration or enrollment

You can browse the websites without registering or enrolling, but you will need to complete a registration or enrollment form in order to take advantage of certain features, such as loading Something Extra coupon offers. By providing us with personal information that you offer voluntarily or that we solicit, you consent to our use of your information in accordance with our privacy policy and applicable laws and regulations.To use some of the features of our websites, you must first complete a registration or enrollment form and create a user name and password. During registration or enrollment, you are required to give contact information (such as name and address or email address). We may use this information to contact you about the services on our sites in which you have expressed interest and/or about products and special offers from our stores.After you submit a completed registration or enrollment form, you may receive a communication acknowledging our receipt of the registration or enrollment.

You can modify your registration or enrollment information anytime. Simply Sign In, click Manage Your Account and edit whatever information you wish.Do not share your password with anyone. Other than on the websites, we will never ask you for your password.

### Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us on-line, we request certain personally identifying information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). When you enter your credit card number on our order form, we encrypt it using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill and/or deliver your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

After you submit a completed order form, you may receive a communication acknowledging our receipt of the order.

### Job Application Forms

If you apply for a job on our site, we require that you provide certain personally identifying information, including your name, address and phone number. This information is necessary to process your application and to contact you. When you enter your personal information on our job application form, we encrypt it using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

After you submit a completed job application, you may receive a communication acknowledging our receipt of the application.

### Prescription Refills

If you request a refill of your prescription on-line, we require that you provide certain personally identifying information, including your last name, birth date, and prescription number. This information is necessary to process your refill. This personally identifying information is subject to the terms and conditions of our pharmacy’s Privacy Notice, which is available on the Web-Fill web page, or you can  [click here to go directly to our pharmacy’s Privacy notice](https://www.raleys.com/www/feature/legal.jsp?featureid=1113647).

### Surveys, Sweepstakes and Contests

From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in voluntary surveys, sweepstakes or contests on our site. If you participate, we may request certain personally identifying information from you. Participation in these surveys, sweepstakes or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. By providing us with personal information that you offer voluntarily or that we solicit, you consent to our use of your information in accordance with our privacy policy and applicable laws and regulations

### Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from, nor are our websites intended for or directed to, children under the age of thirteen. In order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we ask parents to not allow their children under the age of thirteen to provide any personal information on this website. If children under the age of thirteen provide any personal information on our website, their parents or legal guardians should contact us at 800-925-9989 to have this information removed and to unsubscribe their children from any marketing communications from us.

### Uses of Information

We use the information we collect when you visit different sections of our websites to help make our sites, products and services more useful to you. For example, one section of our website may ask for a ZIP Code to help you identify store locations in the vicinity of that ZIP Code or to provide information to you about savings or special offers available in that vicinity.

If you are ordering products or services, your order information will be used and disclosed by Raley’s or its affiliated companies for billing and shipping purposes and to fill and/or deliver your orders.

If you are applying for a job, your application information will be used and disclosed by us, in connection with the application and hiring process. The application information can be used to assess your suitability for employment with Raley’s or its affiliated companies, conduct background investigations or verify information about you, conduct applicant and employment-related statistical evaluation and record keeping, and comply with legal obligations or respond to legal claims.

Your registration or enrollment information may be used to contact you about the services on our sites in which you have expressed interest.

## Communications from the Site

### Special Offers and Updates

If you have completed a registration or enrollment form, we will send you information about your account, products, promotions, services, and personalized offers.

### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifying information you provide us, we may send you a welcoming email to verify your user name and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries and to provide the services you request. We may communicate with you by email, direct mail, telephone, SMS, chat or social media.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We share your personally identifying information with certain agents, representatives, contractors and service providers for limited purposes, including but not limited to, filling customer orders, offering certain products and services in connection with our websites, delivering customer orders to customers, communicating with customers, providing customer service, enhancing and improving customers’ shopping experience, administering or facilitating surveys, sweepstakes or contests, offering targeted marketing communications to customers that opted-in to receive such communications, enabling access to our partners’ websites (for example, ecart), providing a personalized shopping experience, preventing fraud, and completing payment method processing. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with these partners. This aggregated demographic and statistical information that we share with these partners is not linked by us to any personally identifying information that can identify any individual person.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifying information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, to prevent harm or injury, or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

### Controlling Marketing Communications

We may from time to time send you email messages, SMS text messages or other forms of marketing communications describing new items, featured merchandise and great values. You can choose to stop receiving any marketing emails from us at any time by following these steps:

#### Email:

  1. Click the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email communication from Raley’s. You will be taken to your subscription center page
  2. Select or deselect your preferences
  3. Click Update

#### SMS:

If you would like to be removed from receiving text messages, text STOP to 765-765 to opt-out. After texting STOP to 765-765, you will receive one additional message confirming that your request has been processed.

Please allow up to 10 days for us to process your request. If you would prefer to stop receiving other forms of marketing communications from us, please follow the directions on the marketing materials or contact the Raley’s Service Center at 800-925-9989. Even when you elect not to receive marketing emails, you will continue to receive certain emails from us to: confirm any purchases you make on the websites, share other information about your order, respond to your customer service inquiries, and answer any other questions you may have about our websites. In addition, we may also need to send operational emails to inform you of any changes to the websites that might affect your personally identifying information or your access to services. You will receive service and reminder emails if you register or enroll to use certain services offered by our stores, such as the Pharmacy AutoFill service.

### Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in electronic log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the sites, to track users’ movements around the sites and to enhance the experience of our customers on our websites.  We do not link this automatically collected data to your personally identifying information.

### Cookies and Other Computer Information

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. Visitors to our websites are sent anonymous cookies to keep track of their browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile.  
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our sites. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser.

In addition, a user who has clicked on an advertisement on another website that links to raleys.com, nobhill.com, somethingextra.com, shiptohome.raleys.com, shop.raleys.com, pharmacy.raleys.com, foodforfamilies.org, raleysstories.com, raleysletsbegin.com, foodsource.net or any other website hosted by Raley’s or Raley’s affiliates may be sent a persistent cookie that allows us to analyze advertising effectiveness and manage our relationship with the referring website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your browser’s “help” feature.

Persistent cookies are used to customize the content of certain sections of the websites and enable us to track and target the interests of our users and to enhance the experience on our websites. For example, we may set a persistent cookie to store your preferred store locations for weekly ads and promotions, so you don’t have to enter it more than once.  
If you reject cookies, you may still use our sites, but your ability to use some areas of our sites, such as easier access to offers, will be limited.

We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to raleys.com, nobhill.com, somethingextra.com or foodsource.net. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer’s operating system, browser type and the address of a referring website, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to the website.

We also contract with third parties to provide us with: data collection and reporting services regarding our customers’ activities on the websites; tracking and measuring performance of our marketing efforts and your response to our marketing efforts; and the delivery of relevant marketing messages. These third parties may use cookies and Web beacons (1 x 1 pixels), and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on the websites. None of your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address, credit card number, etc.) will be received by or shared with these third parties. If you do not want your non-personal information used to serve ads to you, you should change the settings of your browser to reject cookies.

### Links to Other Sites

Our websites contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Raley’s and its affiliated companies. Please be aware that we, Raley’s and its affiliated companies, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and the privacy polices of such other sites control any activity or transactions you conduct therein.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our sites and to read the privacy statements of each and every website you link to that collects personally identifying information. For example, you have left our websites when you click on the links to Careers, Travel Smart, Gift Card Mall and other similar links.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by us from raleys.com, nobhill.com, somethingextra.com, shop.raleys.com, pharmacy.raleys.com, foodforfamilies.org, raleysstories.com, raleysletsbegin.com, foodsource.net or any other website hosted by Raley’s or Raley’s affiliates.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter certain sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order or job application forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If your browser is capable of SSL, your personally identifying information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent over the Internet.

Your personally identifying information is protected by the password you created when you completed the registration or enrollment form at our website or by another password you created after changing a previous password. Keep your password confidential. No representative of Raley’s will ever ask you for your password.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. But no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our website, you can send an email to us at webmaster@raleys.com.

### Business Transitions

In the event Raley’s or its affiliates go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifying information will likely be transferred.

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement here and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at webmaster@raleys.com.

## Fraud Reporting

### DON’T GET SCAMMED  
Report suspicious emails, text messages and web pages

Your privacy is very important to us. Unfortunately, fraudulent emails, text messages, and webpages are becoming more common and sophisticated, so we’re adding even more safeguards to protect our customers.

If you receive a suspicious email or text message and aren’t sure if it is from Raley’s, Bel-Air, or Nob Hill Foods, it probably isn’t.

DO NOT open attachments, click on links, or respond to emails or text messages if you suspect the email or text message is fake or fraudulent. Instead, please forward the suspicious email to us or send us a new email with a copy of the suspicious text message at [reportphishing@raleys.com](mailto:reportphishing@raleys.com).

If you see a webpage claiming to be ours that seems fake, please copy the link and email it to us at [reportphishing@raleys.com](mailto:reportphishing@raleys.com).

We will investigate and report back to you to if the email, text message or webpage was actually sent or hosted by us.

### LOOK FOR THESE CLUES  
How to spot a phony email, text message, or webpage

If the sender’s email address does not include the raleys.com domain name, instead of using another domain, it’s not from us. Example: raleys@comcast.net.

If the email includes an urgent call to action such as, “For your protection and for security reasons,” or asks you to update your information via a link or button, report the email as it’s likely a scam.

If an email contains a webpage URL that looks like it leads to the Raley’s website, the email might actually be linked to a non-Raley’s webpage, which might be a spoof website. Hover over the link to reveal the real URL and if it’s not from the domain raleys.com, report it.

Fraudulent text messages often use similar techniques as fraudulent emails and typically convey a sense of urgency to secure your account and using words like “limited,” “locked,” or “deactivated” to describe your account status. These text messages may prompt you to call a specific phone number, visit a link, or respond directly with personal or account information.

If the text message originates from a suspicious sender or includes an unprompted request for personal information, report the text message as it’s likely a scam.

If you click on a link, open an attachment, or otherwise respond to a suspicious email, text message, or webpage, or if you have any other security concerns or questions about your account, please [contact us](mailto:reportphishing@raleys.com) immediately.
